<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Digital Mining</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="tap_to_mine">Tap to Mine</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign In</string>
    <string name="email">E-mail</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="dont_have_account">"Don't have an account yet? Sign up."</string>
    <string name="synchronization...">Synchronization...</string>
    <string name="already_have_an_account">Already have an account? Sign In</string>
    <string name="minig">Mining</string>

    <!-- Settings Screen Resources -->
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- SDK Network Email -->
    <string name="sdkNetworkMail" translatable="false">info.sdknetwork@gmail.com</string>

    <!-- Splash Screen Resources -->
    <string name="title_activity_splash_screen" translatable="false">SplashScreenActivity</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Our Privacy Policy:\n\n This privacy policy applies to all services developed and operated by us. These services include our Android mobile application. This policy informs you about how we collect, use and protect your personal information. We care about your privacy and do our best to protect your personal information. \n\nInformation We Collect:\n\n While using our application, we may collect information voluntarily provided by our users. This information may include, but is not limited to, personal and device information such as e-mail address, password. \n\nUse of Information:\n\n We may use the information we collect to provide, improve and personalize our services, make recommendations to our users, take security measures and provide user support. We may also share the information we collect with third parties, but only to help us provide our services. \n\nSecurity:\n\n We take appropriate physical, electronic and managerial measures to ensure the security of our users\' personal information. However, communications over the internet are not absolutely secure and we cannot guarantee that any transmission of information will be completely secure. \n\nCryptocurrency:\n\n Please note: There is no guarantee that the cryptocurrencies obtained by pre-mining with this application will be released to the market. If the cryptocurrency is not released, you do not have any right to claim it back. \n\nChanges:\n\n We reserve the right to update this privacy policy at any time. Our changes will take effect when any updated version is released. Therefore, we recommend that you check this page periodically. \n\nTo be accepted:\n\n By using our application you are deemed to have accepted this privacy policy. If you do not accept this policy, we recommend that you do not use our application. Communication If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please do not hesitate to contact us.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_text">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="password_length">Passwords length should be greater than 5!</string>
    <string name="passwords_matches">Passwords don\'t matches!</string>
    <string name="copied">Copied</string>
    <string name="mining_speed">Mining Speed</string>

</resources>